it was 2006 and I flew from Thailand
where I've been living at the time to
the United States I flew to California
for the San Francisco to do a workshop
training called air otay I was beginning
my journey as a coach and I wanted to
really kind of dive in deep and
something had called to me on from their
website from someone has spoken to who
done the training that this was going to
be significant I was going to learn a
lot so I walked in the door on the first
day of our otay and he will began to
share what they were up to what they
were doing and I said look I'm not here
the same reason the rest of you are high
here it wasn't the personal growth is
for professional development I want to
learn to do what you guys the
facilitators are doing not what the
participants doing well one day in two
days in three days in I'm lying on the
floor crying my heart is broken open
people looking down at me and telling me
how much they love me which doesn't make
sense because why would they do that I'm
a complete mess on the floor and a light
bulb went on you know those tiny
insights that let me have it in sight
everything changes and you can't quite
see what it is well everything changed
10 days later I met Monique and I
proposed to her and I moved permanently
tonight states my career's taken off as
a coach and we now to beautiful baby
boys and I credit so much of that with
the training I did with Alexis and guy
I've never known to coaches we have an
ability to see deep into the heart of
people and and see what you can't even
see that you won't see that what you
can't even see that you need see what
you can't even express into the world
and I am I'm so deeply moved by the work
that i did with them that I went and
trained with him I spent a year going
deeper them and I become friends for a
long time playing with him learning from
them challenging them being challenged
by them and I credit my relationship my
two beautiful babies with the work that
I did the deep work that I did with
Alexis and guy how for stuff powerful
stuff